Autograph Collection 1559-1962 (bulk 1795-1920)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 3: T.E. Hanley Autograph Collection
  - Ruskin, John, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Saxe, John Godfrey, 1863-1865 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Schenck, Gen. R.C., 1865 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Scudder, Horace, 1871-1882 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Simigo, Chas, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Alfred, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Stockton, Frank R., 1891-1894 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Stoddard, R.H., 1872-1900 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Symonds, John Addington, 1890-1891 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Vacarescu, Helene, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Ade, George, 1866-1944 (6 drafts of what appears to be a manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Auden, W.H. (Wystan Hugh) 13 page sonnet, paper entitled “In the time of War: Commentary,” and 1 manuscript entitled “Age of Anxiety”, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Creely, Bunster letter to T.E. Hanley, and radio broadcast script entitled:“I was There.”, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron, 1878-1957, 1922? (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - D’Wolff, John, 1779-1872, 1843 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Forster, John, 1812-1876, 1872 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Ford, Ford Maddox- manuscript, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Garrison, William Lloyd, 1805-1879, 1842 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Janvier, Thomas, 1889-1962, 1892-1893 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Simigo, Chas, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Wegetin, Oscar, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 12)